photomontager.com 2014-07-01

# Privacy Policy - Moonlighting

### Privacy policy

**What information we collect and how we collect it**  
We will not sell, rent or lease your personal information. We will not use your personal information for any purposes other than those outlined in our Privacy Policy and/or in our Terms and Conditions, without your consent.

In order for you to register an account in our websites (PhotoMontager.com,PhotoFacer.com and Paintle.com), we require that you provide us a username, an e-mail address and a password. We use this information only in special cases, such as if we need to contact you, if you request a password reset, etc. A cookie (small text file placed on your computer) is used to automatically identify you as a registered user when you are browsing our site.

Some of our third party advertising partners may use cookies or similar technologies to track the effectiveness of the advertisements they run on our websites. The use of those technologies is subject to the privacy policies of those advertisers and is not to ours.

We use Google Analytics to analyse how our website is used and to improve our website and customer service. Google Analytics may use cookies to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information in an anonymous form.

All user photos updated to our websites or apps are stored in our third party servers for processing purposes only, and are deleted automatically and periodically. Nevertheless, the user of our services agrees that we are not responsible for unintended accidents or hacking of those servers. We recommend the user not to post sensitive information in their photographies.

**Third party links**  
Our websites may contain links to third party websites. These websites should have their own privacy policies, which we recommend to read before submitting any personal data to them.

**Contact us**  
In case of doubt, please contact us via email at [feedback@moonlightsa.com.ar](mailto:feedback@moonlightsa.com.ar)

**Terms of use**  
By using the sites PhotoMontager.com, PhotoFacer.com, Paintle.com, SuperPhotoApp.com, and SuperBannerApp.com and our apps, you agree not to post inappropriate content (including defamatory, abusive, obscene, not-owned, copyrighted, pornographic or illegal). Moonlighting S.A. has the right (but assumes no obligation) to limit access to, edit or delete any material that we consider unacceptable or inappropriate, whether for legal or other reasons.

Any material updated by users must be either purchased under license (e.g., www.featurepics.com), in the public domain, linked under the Creative Commons license, property of the uploader or uploaded with written permission from the owner.

If you find a posted image that is in violation, please report it by clicking on the Report Abuse icon: . We will delete it immediately or add the due credit, if requested.

**Copyright policy (DMCA)**  
Our sites have photo materials that are divided in two categories: 

1\. Site photos: these are photos managed by us, the site owners. These photos are either purchased under license (e.g., www.featurepics.com), in the public domain, linked under the Creative Commons license, of our property or uploaded with the written permission from the owner.

2\. User provided photos: when users create templates, have to explicitly state they either own the material, or they have explicit written permission to use it. We have automatic monitors for certain keywords (like Disney) to disable infringing content. Our site admins also monitor closely the content and disable manually infringing photos. If you find a posted image that is in violation, please report it by clicking on the Report Abuse icon: . We will delete it immediately or add the due credit, if requested.

**Open Source tools used by our apps**  
Our apps use several open-source tools. We are thankful to the developers for their awesome work!  
\- GMIC  
\- ImageMagick  
\- GIMP  
\- GifSicle  
\- Linux/Ubuntu  
\- RRdtool  
\- Nginx  
\- Ruby on rails  
\- Mysql  
\- Django / python 

We are committed to give back to the community. If youre in this list and think we can help or support your work, please contact us to discuss possibilities.
